http://www.lumenlegal.com/privacy

Case Studies
Privacy PolicyLumen Legal, headquartered in Troy, Michigan, is committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information private. Because our website includes areas in which individuals can provide personally identifying information, our Privacy Policy informs our users of our policies and practices regarding the information we collect on our website. If you have further questions about our privacy policies or practices after reading this Privacy Policy, please contact us.ScopeThe Lumen Legal Privacy Policy governs the URL: https://www.lumenlegal.com.PolicyInformation collected about usersLumen Legal collects and maintains certain personal information about a user when such user sends Lumen Legal an email or completes our online Contact Us Form. The personal information provided can identify the user and his or her business individually, and includes items such as user name, email address, job title, company name, address and phone number.Also, depending on the nature of the user’s inquiry or activity on the website and applications, Lumen Legal may also collect the user’s  job search criteria and preferences, employment experience, educational history, skills, references’ information, background information, and other information contained in the user’s  resume, and any login ID or email address created by the user.  For example, by creating a profile and logging into our website, we may use such information to provide the user with information regarding employment opportunities and career-related information, and to otherwise provide user with requested information or services.User information collection meansWhen a user visits Lumen Legal’s website, certain technical information (IP address and domain name) is collected by the website. Lumen Legal cannot use this technical information to identify the user personally. Lumen Legal also collects personal and company information that the user provides to us via the Contact Us Form.  If a user requests a Perspective Paper or other information, Lumen Legal may send the user these materials via email.Lumen Legal does not collect any information from the user online other than the personal information described above; www.lumenlegal.com does not use cookies to collect information about a user for any reason.Use of user informationLumen Legal uses the information a user provides to us to contact the user in response to any requests, complaints or comments the user may have about www.lumenlegal.com.Information is not shared with third partiesLumen Legal (www.lumenlegal.com) does not collect or compile personal information for distribution to parties outside of Lumen Legal, and does not share any information about a user with any parties outside of Lumen Legal. Users will not receive any contact from third parties outside of Lumen Legal as a result of providing information to us, with the possible exception of contact from a website to which we have forwarded a request, complaint, or comment that you have sent to us.Lumen Legal may be required to disclose personal information:  1.) to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, or 2.) to protect Lumen Legal or its client’s  rights, safety or property or, 3.) to a third party to perform a Lumen Legal business function such as hosting its webserver.   Lumen Legal will disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.Protection of children’s online privacyLumen Legal understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment; www.lumenlegal.com is not intentionally designed for or directed at children less than 13 years of age. It is our policy to never knowingly collect or maintain information about individuals under age 13.Links to Outside WebsitesLumen Legal’s website may contain links to third party websites not controlled by Lumen Legal, and not covered by this Privacy Policy, such as those belonging to vendors, job board partners and web and social media sites.  Any information that a user submits, posts, or otherwise reveals through these public forums will be seen by third parties not related to Lumen Legal and may be used by them or Lumen Legal to contact you for any purpose. We recommend that users check the privacy policy of other sites visited.Internal SecurityLumen Legal wants your information to remain as secure as reasonably possible. Lumen Legal combines industry-standard technical safeguards with a code of conduct for those employees who are permitted to access user information. Many of Lumen Legal’s web-based services are hosted on servers that are located at a third-party facility with whom Lumen Legal has a contract providing for security measures.Lumen Legal data may be viewed or accessed by authorized employees, agents, partners or independent contractors only for the purposes of providing our services or as may be required by law.Despite these security measures, Lumen Legal does not represent or warrant that information will be protected against loss, misuse, attacks, or alteration by third parties. Users are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of their usernames and passwords to ensure account security.External SecurityLumen Legal recognizes the importance of safeguarding personal information in our possession from theft, inappropriate use, or improper distribution. While Lumen Legal strives to protect personal information, Lumen Legal cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information a user transmits to us and a user does so at his or her own risk. Please consider the types of information, device security, and internet connection available before submitting any information to Lumen Legal. Ensure only those items publicly available are transmitted to Lumen Legal when you use our website and applications for increased information security.User CommunicationsIn the event that a user transmits e-mail, instant messages, or any other message, information, feedback, data, question, comment, suggestion, or other item to Lumen Legal, such communication shall become the property of Lumen Legal and may be used by Lumen Legal in connection with its operations, services, and business.  Lumen Legal shall have the unrestricted right to any ideas, concepts, know-how, documentation, diagrams, drawings, or techniques contained in a user’s communication in any manner and for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing, creating, or marketing Lumen Legal products and services.Unsubscribe RequestsLumen Legal may, from time to time, use a user’s personal information to send messages or marketing materials regarding Lumen Legal services, including employment information and job opportunities that the user indicated an interest in when creating a profile.  The user may receive these messages from Lumen Legal using various methods, including email, phone, direct mail, and other communication means.Lumen Legal does not, however, want to send a user information that he or she does not wish to receive, and a user may opt out of receiving these communications or change his or her preferences, as indicated below.Email Link. Each email Lumen Legal sends will contain instructions on how to unsubscribe in the event that you do not wish to receive future informational emails from Lumen Legal.Direct Request. You can email us directly to request to be removed from the informational email list by sending the request to contact@lumenlegal.com.Consent to Lumen Legal Privacy Policy & Changes to PolicyBy using the Lumen Legal website or Lumen Legal applications, the user implies acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and the user consents to the collection and use of the information as described herein.Lumen Legal reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason and a user’s continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy.Privacy InquiriesIf at any time a user has questions or concerns about Lumen Legal’s privacy commitment or anything contained in this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact Lumen Legal at the address below, or call 1-877-933-1330 to speak to one of our team members.Our postal address is:Lumen Legal Headquarters1560 E. Maple Road, Suite 400ATroy, MI  48083-1135We can also be reached via e-mail at contact@lumenlegal.com.
